freeparentstuff.co.uk 2010-12-02

# win4now - Privacy

#### Win4now Privacy Policy Statement

This Privacy Policy Statement explains the data processing practices of win4now.co.uk. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail at [privacy@win4now.co.uk](mailto:privacy@win4now.co.uk)

#### Registration & Information Collected

We collect personal information from you through the use of enquiry and registration forms and each time you e-mail us your details.

We also collect information automatically about your visit to our site. This information, which includes demographic data and browsing patterns, is collected via the use of cookies (see below) and session file information.

#### Use of personal information

We use personal information collected via win4now.co.uk to:

  * provide you with information about the products and services we offer
  * provide you with a more personalised service
  * conduct market research
  * run competitions and promotions
  * pass on to selected companies to provide you with other offers and promotions
  * help other companies profile and extend their databases
  * facilitate communication between yourself and others
  * allow us to send you, via e-mail, telephone, SMS and post, details of special offers and promotions from OptinData, Marketing Craze Ltd. and the Heart Reseach Institute. 

We currently only keep "sensitive data", as defined by the Data Protection Act 1998 for the explicit purpose of providing initial and renewal car insurance quotations.

#### Use of cookies

We use "cookies" to identify you when you visit the win4now.co.uk site and to build up a profile of our regular users.

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser. Our use of cookies also allows members to be presented with a personalised version of the site.

We will only read cookies from your cookie file placed there through your web browser's interaction with the win4now site. [ aboutcookies.org ](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)

#### Use of session files

We use session files, along with cookies, to log your browsing patterns and so identify the areas of the site which have been of interest to you, allowing us to personalise the win4now site for you.

We also use information in aggregate form (in other words, no individual user is identified) to:

  * to build up marketing profiles
  * to allow us to develop the business in ways that help you
  * to manage our relationship with advertisers and
  * to audit usage of the site

All personal, cookie and session ID information are made available to win4now call centre employees to enable us and any related third parties to deal more effectively with any enquiry you make.

#### Your control over the use of your personal data

You have complete control over the use of your personal information by win4now.

We want the opportunity to make you offers and unless you are willing to agree to this you can't enter the competitions. However this permission can be revoked at any time through your account page or via an email unsubscribe link. If you do decide to revoke it, then competition entries already made will remain in force. 

Consent to the transfer of your personal data to service providers acting for DMR who may be based outside the EEA and that DMR will take all reasonable required steps to ensure that your data and privacy rights continue to be protected 

No data will be retained through the use of the "refer a friend" mechanism other than to notify the friend until that friend then decides to join and register with the site 

Our site links to other web sites and we are not responsible for the content on those sites or their data policies and procedures.

#### Security

We use 128 bit encryption technology for the transmission from you to us of financially sensitive data, i.e. credit card details, but cannot guarantee the security of any other data you send to us.

#### Data Protection

win4now.co.uk is wholly owned by [Data Media and Research Limited](http://www.dmri.co.uk/), which is registered under the 1998 Data Protection Act, ref Z4579096
